mygnrforum.com 2012-10-15

# MYGNRFORUM - Privacy Policy

#### PRIVACY POLICY

**1\. What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers mygnrforum's treatment of personally identifiable information that mygnrforum collects when you are on the mygnrforum site, and when you use mygnrforum's services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that mygnrforum does not own or control, or to people that mygnrforum does not employ or manage. 

**2\. Information Collection and Use**

mygnrforum collects personally identifiable information when you register for a mygnrforum account, when you use certain mygnrforum products or services, and when you visit mygnrforum pages. When you register with mygnrforum, we ask for your name, email address, and geographic location. Once you register with mygnrforum and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. mygnrforum also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, mygnrforum cookie information and the page you requested. mygnrforum uses information for two general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services (webpages), and to contact you about promotions and site changes. 

No information from children under 13 has knowingly been gathered. Children under the age of 13 are asked not to participate with any interactive part of this site. This is in compliance with The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. 

**3\. Information Sharing and Disclosure**

mygnrforum will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. mygnrforum may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people in response to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or we find that your actions on our web sites violate the mygnrforum User Agreement. 

**4\. Cookies**

mygnrforum may set and access mygnrforum cookies on your computer. The exclusive purpose of these cookies is to maintain 'state', such as whether or not you are logged in to your account. No personally-identifiable information, aside from possibly your login name, is stored in these cookies. mygnrforum's cookies and their contents are NOT available to other parties or websites. 

**5\. Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

mygnrforum gives you the ability to edit your mygnrforum Account Information and preferences at any time. You may request deletion of your mygnrforum account by contacting a site administrator using the personal messaging system, or by an email to webmaster@mygnrforum.com. 

**6\. Security**

Your mygnrforum Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas, mygnrforum may utilize industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

**7\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

mygnrforum may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages, and at our discretion, optionally e-mailing all users. 

**8\. Copyright**

See the terms of service for more information about copyright and other intellectual property at <http://www.mygnrforum.com/public/tos.html>. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions please contact us by email at webmaster@mygnrforum.com
